So, as you can see, I scrap all of the data, and I see all of the search engines here.
And with the model, you can try to write a simple script.
And when we have a graphic, we see country name.
And we see the source URL that we use.
So, for the first thing, I will open a new agent because it will be a new feature.
First, I am going to, I will use the legend because I didn't need a plan.
I want you to update this project, I have a new data, and I will make like a reference
to do it, and I want you to ask the implement it in our search engine context.
But first, I want you to remove all of Google data and save only local ones.
Please, do not change current search engines, just populate with additional ones, and create
the code folder for each country that has at least one valid search engine.
And so, it's more advanced, so first you will probably just populate the data, keep the
domain if you have a script like this, and you want to clear it out, it might apply some
changes here, so it's better to have a copy somewhere around, and then basically copy
it to the project, and then have a connection, and then we can obviously drag and drop here,
to make a reference, so it will process engine and I will actually run it, it will require
some of it.
So, first, it will create a JavaScript, and I figured to remove, I would like to keep it
simple, because I would like to have only one file like it was before, because previously
we just had a manifest and background JavaScript, so this time it will just create a script
to make it automatically, and then we will remove it, because I want to just keep like
a simple as it is, because in the future, I will release that search scrapper directly
on Google, so we are able to test it out, and I want to show how the entire process looks,
like especially when you release your extension, so I will use it, and then I will just
upload it, so as we can see, it's creating a script to match all the data, and then I will
just use the extension tab that is directly here, and I will refresh, alright, the extension
now supports 192 countries, the existing engines are preserved, and hundreds of new local
search engines has been added, have been added, and all temporal process scripts have been
cleaned up, and like I said before, and those scripts were removed, they would just
temporary to extract the data, because manually creating that, it would take a lot of time,
and just take a few minutes, because yeah, I just work perfect for that.
Actually that extension from here, we can remove it, and we have like some readme file,
and I'm not sure if we need this thing, but what I'm going to do is first this it out,
so now we just refresh the search, always see the some errors, okay, and service work
registration failed, so if there's like a syntax error, what I'm going to do, I can just
kind of remove it background, and the most function, stack trace, so I will just use it,
then apply it here, and do I need this, because we know that in the background probably
is quite a lot here, we see a lot of things, I want to keep it simple, with JS file, and
let me try to see the manifest file, okay, the manifest is obviously needed, and there
readme we can actually move it as well, I will just keep it for now, keep it anyway,
we can switch as well between, you control i, and I'll just switch between asian plan
and ask, so first it will just quote a lot of the numeric prices to fix the syntax error,
we have only two remaining files, except readme, and I will keep it as now, and we can
see the background is just one JavaScript file, it contains almost 2,000 lines, and I think
I'm going to test it out now, so I'll just go to the extension tab, I want to make extension
tab, I will go again to manager, like manager extension, I would refresh it again, alright,
and there's some still errors, I'm not sure what is it ever to clear out, and I will
go again to my extension, I will refresh, okay, so this is the one, and let me function,
I'll go to hacker news now, and then I can go to any website and try to lose the searchers,
so this is the assembly, and I will go and search, and back until we have everything
now, that's pretty awesome, so I think there are too many countries, so I would divide
it by continents, because we can divide it in the previous website, to Europe, to Europe,
to Asia, to Africa, but I will first try, okay, I will use maybe Iran, and I will use
this, and maybe I will use again, and I will use something like popular one, so I will go
to Croatia, maybe have like other ones, like some photography, and says no, it's assembly,
okay, so I think it's working, great, and what I'm going to do, I will go back and see
the extension error, first I would like to fix it, we can view in the dev tools how it
looks like, first I just don't see, so it's like context anonymous function, I use this
kind of stuff, I can clear it out, and maybe refresh, so this is the one that I get, and
we'll discover it over, I want you to look at these two errors, I will copy it, extension
working, but I have this notifications in Chrome extension panel, so I will just use it,
because obviously if you add it to a market, we have to make it without, so maybe we just
see, maybe it will fix correctly, and then after that I will open a new agent, because
now I'm using the new agent, we can as well, scan you one, and I, in the new one, it will
just add some new changes, so this one is working on something, so I will run a parallel
agent, and the parallel agent is going to do, I think the list of countries is too long,
for scrolling, I want you to add a subfolder that will display countries by continent,
and I can say like example Europe, Croatia, Asia, we can say Japan, and let me see
a new updated, alright, we see the change, so we change, and now we'll run another
agent, and we see if it can work on it, and then after that I will extend, I refresh
it, so first I will wait for an extension, because I would like to have it more categorized,
okay, it runs some of the comments, I will always, and obviously we can always go back
or like run a new branch, if you want to create a test a new issue, if you want to create
like a new stuff, and go back, for example when we are testing functionalities in more
advanced software, it has been finished, so now I will go to extension type again, I will
go to my extension library, I will refresh it, unfortunately there is still one error, okay,
so the stuff will become, I will just remove it, remove it, and if it pops up, actually
it's now working, so now if I open a new tab, then we will go to the first place from
Hacking Us, okay, and this is like some simulation stuff, so maybe I will open like some
log to have a stuff that I would like to see, outside Rubik, and now if I search with,
I search by country, I see, it's here, that's pretty, actually awesome, but we do have
a dominant, and there's like Uzbekistan Yemen, and there is in Africa, so they have even
all of it, and I think I would like to remove, yeah, it was because it works like similar
to Rubik, and there are not other things, I don't see like America, so I will have to ask
another stuff, now go to background, and try to see for something, so Slovenia, but we
are trying to tell you, for example, okay, but I don't see that in America, or Australia,
I'll see this, at remaining continents, so run the agent again, it's nice because we see it has
added some folders, and I see folders and it's just changing, so this is the main engines
that we can always try to adapt, and then after that, I'll add a new feature, before
publishing, to be better to check everything, so at the very bottom, we see all of the countries,
and each country has its own assign continent here, and some names, go to your row, okay,
sometimes we see like some, the same addresses, so this is like an unknown one, the problem
is that it would like to remove it, because we have like a bulb of it, so the main stuff
we can do, we probably have to go run another check, or another query, because if we go
down search, and we go to Poland again, we're just trying to use it, and you see that one
as well, it's not longer working, so what I'm going to do, I will clear up all this, because
some of it is not working, I will go to the game, and some websites like, actually we should
clear out data before implementing it, because I just scrapped the data, but some of the
websites we are not working, what I'm going to do, so websites like, and root of all, it's not working, I think we should try and ping each side, and those that are not unspringing, are not longer,
verbal, should be removed, and I will use this as a new agent, and obviously we can organize it,
about how we'll just clear out the data, so enter it, and we'll be a new agent, in progress, so first it will just try to identify and remove it, and in the meantime I can actually
this is called Oceania, so I might need it, because we want to have this assignment, your for example has a lot, but what if I go to the very
top of it, to one, and here I see like a folder, because it's just European, so I can go to very last of it, like 50, and I realized there are some
countries that are no longer available, like Yugoslavia, I realized there are some countries that are no longer apparently existing, so
I see we save a time out, it will improve your all testing, I have to run it,
and now pause the video, because the list is very big, I'll try to use it, I've gone webs, let's come, as we can see the set cannot be reached, so first we'll clear the data,